Thomas DiBenedetto

Indeed Intern

Cypress, TX - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Thomas-DiBenedetto/453d2d33cc72b36f

Result-oriented college freshman dedicated to advancing innovation in computer systems. Demonstrates significant aptitude for quickly absorbing and successfully applying concepts and programming languages. Dedicated to increasing knowledge and experience in the sciences of computing and mathematics.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Intern

Indeed - Austin, TX - May 2012 to Present

Intern

Hewlett-Packard - Houston, TX - December 2010 to August 2011

Worked as a high school intern programming internal projects meant for graphical representation of data

EDUCATION

BS - Turing Scholar in Computer Science

University of Texas at Austin - Austin, TX 2011 to 2015

SKILLS

Java, C, MongoDB, MySQL,